PROFILE

I have 3+ years of experience in IT industry, worked with HCL technologies as a Backup admin using Veritas Netbackup tool and HPSM. I also got professional 3 months training on Devops.

Currently, working with 3 Pillar Global as a Senior Software Engineer in Devops role, working on AWS managed infrastructure for both Linux and Windows. And using Jenkins for deployment, also well versed with CI/CD implementation using Jenkins. Worked on Ansible for configuration management.

I am Devops professional and always ready to grab new opportunities and learning new things.

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Sysops Administrator - Associate

CONTACT

PHONE: 9953612166

LinkedIn Url: www.linkedin.com/in/vishwas-gandhi-041059a6

EMAIL: vishwaslondon@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Gym Listening to Music

VISHWAS GANDHI

Senior Software Engineer (Devops Role)

EDUCATION

Vidya College of Engineering, Meerut - India

2011 - 2015

Did B. Tech in Electrical and Electronics

Saraswati Vihar Senior Secondary School, Saharanpur - India 2010- 2011

I completed my intermediate college at this time with PCM.

Saraswati Vihar Senior Secondary School, Saharanpur - India 2008- 2009

I completed my High School at this time

WORK EXPERIENCE

[3 Pillar Global - Senior Software Engineer (Devops Role) October 2018 - Till now

Working on 4 different AWS managed accounts on both Linux and Windows. Also using Jenkins for deployment and Ansible for configuration management. 24*7 monitoring of AWS accounts using cloud watch and New Relic.

Worked as Freelancer - Devops Specialist

May 2018 - September 2018

I worked on AWS managed production environment and deploying micro-services using AWS's code deploy and Jenkins. Monitoring via cloud watch, New Relic and Loggly.

Work Closely on CI/CD implementation using Jenkins

HCL Technologies - Backup Analyst

September 2015 - April 2018

Here I worked on backup tools such as – Veritas Netbackup and HPDP. I also worked in ticketing tool namely – HPSM.

24*7 monitoring of backups

Removal and addition of servers in Backup Got internal training on AWS and Devops tool.

SKILLS

Jenkins, Ansible, AWS, Maven, GIT, Vagrant, GIT HUB, GITLAB, Docker, Terraform, Linux, BITBUCKET.